mpdedicated.com 2017-06-24

# Privacy Policy - Midphase

## Midphase Privacy Policy

### Effective Date: August 22, 2014

This Privacy Policy discusses how Hosting Services, Inc. (HSI) collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from our customers, visitors to our websites, individuals who contact us and visitors to our customers’ websites (all: “User” or “Users”). Please review our Privacy Policy in conjunction with our Acceptable Use Policy (AUP) and, if applicable, your contract with us. The terms of this Privacy Policy are in addition to the terms of our AUP and contract. The purpose of this Privacy Policy is to provide Users with an understanding of what types of information we collect, how we treat it, and choices they may have related to this information. We reserve the right to change our Privacy Policy at any time. Any changes to this Privacy Policy, other than necessary to remedy typographical errors, will be announced on our home page, as well as in email to the primary address Users have on file with us.

Upon request, we provide Users with access to all information they have provided to us. Users can access this information by e-mailing us at [billing@midphase.com](mailto:billing@midphase.com). If their personally identifiable information changes, Users may correct, update, or delete inaccuracies through [https://secure.mpcustomer.com](https://secure.mpcustomer.com/). If Users are having trouble accessing the contact address above, our customer support team can assist them, and they can be contacted at [1-866-MIDPHASE]() option 2. Users may also contact us at the address below to correct, amend or delete information we maintain about them.

HSI complies with the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework as set forth by the [U.S. Department of Commerce](https://www.commerce.gov/page/eu-us-privacy-shield) regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information transferred from the European Union to the United States. HSI has certified to the Department of Commerce that it adheres to the Privacy Shield Principles. If there is any conflict between the terms in this privacy policy and the Privacy Shield Principles, the Privacy Shield Principles shall govern. To learn more about the Privacy Shield program, and to view our certification, please visit <https://www.privacyshield.gov/>.

Individuals have the right to access their personal data after careful screening of account verification and security protocol. Personal data will not be disclosed to third parties. HSI will be subject to investigatory and enforcement powers of the Federal Trade Commission (FTC) if necessary. HSI will also assume liability in cases of onward transfers to third parties.

## Information Collection and Use

### Orders

If Users purchase a product or service from us, we request personally identifiable information from them on our order form. Users must provide contact information (such as name, email and mailing address) and financial information (such as credit card number, CVV and expiration date). During the purchase process, Users may provide optional information to us. If that information is provided, it is covered by this Privacy Policy; however, providing it is voluntary. Credit card information is made secure by a High-grade Encryption (AES-256, 256 bit keys) Comodo SSL Certificate.

We use this information for billing purposes and to fill a User’s orders. If we have trouble processing an order, we will use this information to contact the User.

### Customer Testimonials

We post User’s testimonials/comments/reviews on our website which may contain personally identifiable information. We do obtain the User’s consent via email prior to posting the testimonial to post their name along with their testimonial. Users may contact us in writing at [sales@midphase.com](mailto:sales@midphase.com) to have their testimonial removed. We will remove it in 30 days.

### Tell-A-Friend

If Users choose to use our referral service to tell a friend about our site, we will ask the User for their friend's name and email address. We will automatically send the User’s friend the User’s personal message via email. HSI stores this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email and tracking the success of our referral program. Users or the User’s friend may request deletion of this information by contacting us in writing at [sales@midphase.com](mailto:sales@midphase.com). This information will be removed in 30 days.

### Customer Service

We will communicate with Users in response to their inquiries, to provide the services they request, and to manage the Users’ account. We will communicate with Users by email or telephone, in accordance with their wishes.

### Surveys or Contests

From time-to-time we may provide Users the opportunity to participate in contests or surveys. If Users choose to participate, we may request certain personally identifiable information from them. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and Users therefore have a choice whether or not to disclose this information. The requested information may include contact information, demographic information, and personal preferences. We may use a third party service provider to conduct these surveys or contests; that provider is prohibited from using our Users' personally identifiable information for any other purpose. Users may request deletion of this information by contacting us in writing at [sales@midphase.com](mailto:sales@midphase.com). The information will be removed in 30 days.

### Registration and Support 

The forms found on our website are used to gather contact information (such as name, email address, billing information, and phone number) of Users to process orders, respond to questions and requests. If Users need to change their personal account information, they may update it by making the change in their account.

We do not intentionally collect information from children under the age of 13.

HSI keeps records of User interaction and support provided (via chat, phone, and email) to track account history and better assist our Users. When Users contact HSI for support for their services, Users will be asked to match certain information that is in their Registration Information. This Registration Information will be used to identify Users personally. In the course of providing support to Users, HSI may annotate the Registration Information with information disclosed while providing support (Support Information).

Support Information may identify Users individually. In addition to providing support to Users, HSI may disclose Support Information to third-party vendors in order to provide the support requested by Users. These third parties may disclose and use Support Information to improve their business processes and for marketing. Unless necessary to provide support to Users, HSI will not disclose Support Information containing information that identifies Users individually to these third parties. During a support request, Users may request that HSI not disclose Support Information to third parties. This request will prevent HSI from providing support to Users.

## Tracking Technologies

### Log Files

HSI gathers certain information automatically and stores it in log files. This information includes Internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data.

### Visitors to Our Website

HSI’s web servers collect information from visitors to the website linked to this Privacy Policy. Because each User’s computer and browser configurations are different, we may collect some, or all, of the following information during their visit:

  1. Internet protocol address;
  2. The type of browser or computer used;
  3. The number of links clicked within HSI’s website;
  4. The state or country from which our website was accessed;
  5. The date and time of visit;
  6. The name of Internet service provider used to access our website;
  7. The web page visited prior to coming to our website; and
  8. The pages viewed on HSI’s website.

We use this information to improve our website, services and user experience, as well as communicate with contest participants. 

### Cookies

A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a Users’ computer for record-keeping purposes. We use cookies on this site. We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information that Users submit while on our site.

We use session ID cookies to make it easier for Users to navigate our site. A session ID cookie expires when Users close their browser. 

If Users reject cookies, they may still use our site, but their ability to use some areas of our site, such as our shopping cart, will be limited.

### Clear Gifs

We employ a software technology called clear gifs (also known as web beacons/web bugs) that help us better manage content on our site by informing us what content is effective. Clear gifs are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the online movements of web users. In contrast to cookies, which are stored on a User's computer hard drive, clear gifs are embedded invisibly on web pages and are about the size of the period at the end of this sentence. We do not tie the information gathered by clear gifs to our User’s personally identifiable information. 

We may also use clear gifs in our HTML-based emails to let us know which emails have been opened by recipients. This allows us to gauge the effectiveness of certain communications and the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns. If Users would like to opt out of these emails, please click the "unsubscribe" link in the email footer. 

We use clear gifs, which do not identify individual Users, to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track Users' movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our customer base as a whole. We do not link this automatically collected data to personally identifiable information. 

We use the following third-party tracking services: Google Analytics, DirectTrack, which use cookies and web beacons to track non-personally identifiable information about visitors to our site in the aggregate of IP addresses to track marketing efforts and affiliate sales. We have no access or control of these third-party tracking technologies. Each of these services works differently; however, they all collect information related to the website from which Users came to HSI, Users’ operating system, browser type, where Users go on HSI’s website, length of time on our website, and where Users go after visiting our website. In addition, these services may keep Users logged into HSI’s system. From time-to-time, HSI may use services that will be used to serve advertising and other information to Users after they visit our website. Because the technologies underlying these services differ, Users may, or may not, be able to choose not to provide information to them.

### Email Correspondence

HSI will use Users’ names and email addresses to send newsletters to them. These newsletters include information on promotions, services, and company information. Out of respect for User privacy, we provide Users a way to unsubscribe in each promotional email. 

We will send Users service-related announcements on occasion when it is necessary to do so; for example, if there is network maintenance, Users will receive an email. Users may opt out of these communications by clicking the unsubscribe link provided.

If Users do not want to receive our newsletter and promotional communications, they may opt out of receiving them by following the instructions included in each newsletter or communication or by emailing us at: [sales@midphase.com](mailto:sales@midphase.com).

### Third-Party Sharing

We will share Users’ personal information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this Privacy Policy. These third parties include credit card processors, technology vendors chosen by Users to be included in the services, and bandwidth providers. We do not sell User personal information to third parties except as described in this Privacy Policy. We may also disclose User personal information: as required by law, such as to comply with a subpoena, or similar legal process; when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect User safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request and; to any other third party with the User’s prior consent to do so. 

HSI may aggregate information covered by this Privacy Policy and disclose it outside our business. This information will not identify Users individually.

In cases of onward transfer to third parties of data of EU individuals received pursuant to the EU-US Privacy Shield, Uk2Group remains liable.

### Linked/Advertiser Sites

From time-to-time, we may include links or banners for third-party sites, including sites that advertise. This privacy policy does not govern the information these sites collect when you visit them. These sites will know that you have visited them from our site.

### Security

The security of Users’ personal information is important to us. We use commercially reasonable standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. When Users enter sensitive information (such as a credit card number) on our order forms, we encrypt the transmission of that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). Electronic communication (for example: email, online chat, or instant messaging) that Users may send HSI may not be secure unless HSI advises Users in advance that security measures will be in place prior to transmitting the information. Users should not send confidential information such as financial information, social security numbers or passwords to HSI through unsecured electronic communication. 

### Data Retention

We will retain User’s information for as long as their account is active or as needed to provide Users services. If Users wish to cancel their account or request that we no longer use their information to provide them services, contact us at [billing@midphase.com](mailto:billing@midphase.com). We will retain and use User information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements. Following termination of the Users’ agreement with us, Users will have no access to this information, and we may delete it for any reason, at any time.

We retain your information for up to 24 months, and often beyond, following your last transaction with us

### Dispute Resolution

If you do not receive timely acknowledgement of your complaint, or if your complaint is not satisfactorily addressed, you can also submit your complain to Privacy Trust, an independent third party. Visit [(https://www.privacytrust.com/drs/uk2group)](https://www.privacytrust.com/drs/uk2group) to file a complaint.

Finally, as a last resort and in limited situations, EU individuals may seek redress from the Privacy Shield Panel, a binding arbitration mechanism. 

### Business Transitions

In the event HSI goes through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, Users’ personally identifiable information will likely be among the assets transferred. Users will be notified via e-mail of any such change in ownership or control of their personal information.

### Contact Us

If Users have any questions or suggestions regarding our Privacy Policy, please contact us at: [1-866-MIDPHASE](), or [sales@midphase.com](mailto:sales@midphase.com). However, if a particular section of this Privacy Policy has a specific contact point, Users must use that point.

HSI  
Marketing - Re: Privacy Policy  
517 W 100 N, Suite 225  
Providence, UT 84332  
Last Updated: July 1, 2014  

Call us at 1-866-643-7427 or  Chat with us
